# SCOTT BROWN



scott\_brown\_jp@yahoo.com | (407) 690-3967 Orlando, FL 32827

Sbrown146.github.io

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Data analyst with a B.S in Statistics from the University of Central Florida with both basic and advanced certifications in SAS, proficiency with R and newly acquired skills in Python, Javascript, and SQL. Proven analytical proclivity with years of experience processing and projecting sales data for private business. Particular inclination for times series data analysis and the capacity to format poorly structured data into pliable and distributive forms. Driven desire and intuition to leave no possible area of a given data set hidden. Flourishes in environments where analytical skills can be applied, and further knowledge can be acquired.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Overnight Baker | Panera Bread - Orlando, FL

01/2013 - 09/2013

- Completed overnight bake for multiple different stores including solo baking.
- Helped complete opening bakes for multiple new bakeries.
- Managed and completed daily upkeep and cleaning for the bakeries.

**Team Leader, Kitchen Manager** | Chick-Fil-A Inc. - Orlando, FL

07/2003 - 09/2012

- Handled nightly operations and closing procedures as kitchen manager.
- Routinely opened and closed store in any needed position.
- Managed multiple tasks at once for front counter and kitchen.
- Trained new employees on both front register and in the kitchen.
- Completed truck order and stocked store twice a week.
- Collected and interpreted food and sales data for statistical analysis and projections.

## Overnight Loader | UPS - Orlando, FL

12/2007 - 03/2008

- Loaded package cars and trailers.
- Loaded multiple units everyday.
- Helped load any other unloaded package cars to meet 8:30am daily deadline.

# Call Center Representative | SunPass - Orlando, FL

05/2007 - 08/2007

- Provided excellent and personal customer service.
- Assisted customers with their sunpass accounts.
- Handled and processed confidential account and credit card information.
- Processed toll violations for sunpass account holders.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Central Florida - Orlando, FL

12/2014

**Bachelor of Science**: Statistics

• Relevant coursework includes: Time Series Analysis and Forecasting, Biostatistics, Sample Survey Methods, Statistical Theory, Nonparametric Statistical Analysis, Derivative Markets

Valencia College - Orlando, FL 12/2010

**Associate of Science**: General Studies

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

SAS Basic SAS Advanced Exam P Exam FM